So now we know which paper types are most popular and we have
حتى الآن، ندرك أنواع الورق الأكثر شيوعًا،
a sense of the largest order size we might need to fulfill at any given time.
ونتفهم حجم الطلب الكبير الذي قد نحتاج إلى تلبيته في أي وقت.
But what's the average order size?
لكن ما متوسط حجم الطلب؟
What can we expect to see on a regular basis?
ما يمكن أن نتوقع رؤيته على أساس منتظم؟
We'll use the average function which is typed as
سنستخدم الدالة المتوسطة التي يتم كتابتها على أنها
AVG and has a similar syntax to all of the other aggregation functions.
AVG ولها بنية مشابهة لجميع دالات التجميع الأخرى.
So it looks like that large poster paper order must have been a major outlier
لذا يبدو أن طلب ورق الملصق الكبير يجب أن يكون كبيرًا جدًا
because the average poster order is only
لأن متوسط حجم طلب الملصق
about a third the size of the average standard order.
لا يتعدى ثلث حجم الطلب القياسي العادي.
When you're using the average function,
عند استخدام الدالة المتوسطة،
keep in mind that it can only be used on numerical columns.
تذكر أنه لا يمكن استخدامها إلا في الأعمدة الرقمية.
Also, it ignores nulls completely,
كما أنه يتم تجاهل القيم الخالية تمامًا،
meaning that rows with null values are not counted in
مما يعني أنه لا يتم حساب الصفوف ذات القيم الخالية في
the numerator or the denominator when calculating the average.
البسط أو المقام عند حساب المتوسط.
If you want to treat nulls as zero,
إذا كنت تريد معالجة القيم الخالية كقيم صفرية،
you'll need to take a sum and divide it by
فستحتاج إلى أخذ المجموع وتقسيمه
the count rather than just using the average function.
على العدد بدلاً من استخدام الدالة المتوسطة فقط.